<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Carson Quigley</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Carson Quigley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 22:14:30 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Me!</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 22:14:30 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>The easiest way to contact me is by email: carson.ll.quigley@gmail.com.
You can also find me on Linkedin or github!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer 2018 - Scheduling Problem in Big Data Workflows</title>
      <link>/projects/summer2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 21:29:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/summer2018/</guid>
      <description>A Brief Synopsis During the Summer of 2018 I worked with Dr. Aravind Mohan to deconstruct
algorithms that attempted to solve the well known Scheduling Problem in the realm of cloud computing. This research led to my presentation of a poster detailing our work towards the end of the research period.
Scheduling Problem The scheduling problem in the field of computer science and cloud computing is a problem in which there are</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer 2017 - Postmodernist Studies</title>
      <link>/projects/summer2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 21:29:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/summer2017/</guid>
      <description>A Brief Synopsis My work over the summer of 2017 with Professor Xiaoling Shi was about postmodernism and the influances it had on
the particular work, A Death In Chicago by Xianyoung. I did much reasearch on postmodernist works during the 1920&amp;rsquo;s era
that may have influanced Xianyoung&amp;rsquo;s work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post!</title>
      <link>/blogs/blog1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 20:51:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/blog1/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes one looks to the first post to find out what the original philosophy of the post creator was.
Wonder what this post&amp;rsquo;s philosophy is..</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second Post!</title>
      <link>/blogs/blog2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 20:51:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/blog2/</guid>
      <description>When looking at posts, one often can use the first few to get an idea of not only the original goals of the project, but also an idea of how the creator was going about achieving those goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 13:49:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Carson Quigley Currently a student at Allegheny College, enjoys working in many programming languages
such as C, Java, Python, Bash, Lua, and more!
I&amp;rsquo;m a huge fan of the linux Operating System and do much of my work from my Google pixelbook running Debian with crouton! I also run ArchLinux on most of my computers including my home desktop.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>